

# **Anisur Rahman**

#### **SUMMARY**

I've more than 1.5 years of working experience in PHP, Laravel, jQuery, VueJS, Nuxt JS and MYSQL. Apart from this stack, I know Django, Django REST Framework, and ExpressJs. I've also knowledge about Machine Learning and Deep Learning. I graduated in Computer Science and Engineering from Southeast University.

#### **SKILLS**

Frontend: CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, NUXT JS, VUE JS

Backend: PHP, Laravel, Express JS

Database: MYSQL, MongoDB Others: AXIOS, WordPress

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Associate Software Engineer SSL Wireless

January 2024 - Present, Dhaka, Bangladesh

- Coordinate requirements, schedules, and activities; contribute to team meetings; and troubleshoot development and production problems across multiple environments and operating platforms.
- · Collaborate with a team to define, design, and ship new features.
- · Collaborating with the design team on developing micro-services.
- Develop REST API for the Frontend team and the Flutter team.

# **Software Developer**

#### **Automate IT Limited**

October 2023 - December 2023, Dhaka

- · Work closely with UI/UX designers to implement responsive and visually appealing interfaces that enhance the learning experience.
- · I`ve to develop REST API for their Product using Laravel. Sometimes integrate API in the frontend in NUXT JS. Design web pages according to the Figma file using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.
- · Projects: Institute Management System, Learning Management System Etc.

## **Software Developer**

#### **Fair News Service Limited**

July 2022 - August 2023, Dhaka

- Design and implement scalable, robust, and maintainable web applications using PHP Laravel.
- Collaborate with front-end developers and other team members to integrate user-facing elements with server-side logic. Optimize applications for maximum speed and performance.
- · I worked here as a full-stack developer. I developed here website using CSS, Bootstrap, and Jquery according to the pre-defined UI design. After completing frontend design developed this website using PHP, Laravel and MYSQL. Maintaintence their existing project.
- · Projects: NewsPortal, Accounting Management System, Price Compering Website, Consulting Website etc.

## Software Developer - Intern ZakirSoft

February 2021 - May 2021, Dhaka

- · I had to develop REST API using Laravel. Then integrate this API into the NUXT JS application.
- · Projects: E-commerce API, LMS API etc.

## **EDUCATION**

## **Bsc in Computer Science and Engineering**

Southeast University • Dhaka, Bangladesh • 2024 • 3.84

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

## **Docker Training Course**

KodeKloud • 2023

· I learned about basic docker commands, how to create docker images, containers etc.

#### **SQL Certificate**

HackerRank • 2022

#### **INVOLVEMENT**

#### **Extended Executive Member and Web Instructor**

Southeast University • Southeast University Computer Club • April 2019 - June 2022

· I was an extended member and web instructor in this club. I took programming-related sessions here like Data Structure Algorithm and Web Design.